

EDUCATION

2022

Designboat UI/UX School, Bangalore, India

2015-2020

B.Arch, Department of Architecture, Anna University, Chennai, India

SKILLS

Software	Design
Figma	UX Research
Sketch	Qualitative Analysis
Invision	Quantitative Analysis
SketchUp 3D	UX Design
Adobe XD	Web/Mobile Design
Adobe Photoshop	Wireframing
Adobe Illustrator	UI Design
Adobe Indesign	Prototype & Test

Programming

HTML CSS

Bootstrap JavaScript

LANGUAGES

English, Tamil, Hindi

GEERTHIKA LAKSHMANAN

UI/UX Designer

Tamilnadu 630301, India argeerthi14@gmail.com

+91 9095232109

LinkedIn

Portfolio Link:

www.geerthika.com

ABOUT

A blend of UI/UX and Architecture. With 2+ years of experience in design field, I love working at the intersection of creativity and User Centered Design. My expertise has been in E-commerce, WEB 3.0, HealthCare, Fintech products - App Design, Web Design, UI Design, UX Research, HTML5, CSS3. I'm open to relocation for the right opportunity.

EXPERIENCE

UX UI Designer (Oct 2022 - Present)

GeekyAnts, Bangalore - Product company, Experience in Design system, Stakeholder interviews, Competitive Analysis, Qualitative Analysis, Quantitative Analysis, Testing.

User Experience Designer (June 2022 - August 2022)

Redd Experience Design (Short period due to company shut down) - B2C Worked on the crypto web projects, I contributed to the task of redesigning the marketing collaterals for the brand Persistence One with UX Research, Information Architecture and Interface Design including the pitch deck, BNB Deck, and PStake.

UI UX Designer (June 2021 - May 2022)

Freelance Designer B2B - Worked on products, with design system, Qualitative Analysis, Quantitative Analysis, User flow, competitive analysis, research, wireframe, UI Design. Collaboration with startsups in Design Branding, Logo, Concept art, Colour theory, Social media management. (Collaboration: Lacasa Studio, Kanoji Design studio, Chui Huay Lim Teochew Cusine, Singapore, Black Architects)

Junior Designer (Jan 2020 - Oct 2021)

HCP design Planning & Management pvt.ltd, Ahmedabad - Worked on the project of 'Central Vista Redevelopment of India, Delhi'. Involved in Indian government presentation deliverables. Communication and Visual Design.

Internship (June 2018 - March 2019)

SR+A Architects, Mumbai - Architecture Internship